Guide to the Truman A. Warner Papers MS 026
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Sheet Music
  - Songs
    - Gee, But It's Great to Meet a Friend From Your Home Town composer: Wm. Tracey/Jas. McGavisk publisher: J. Fred Helf, 1910 (Box 45, Item 73)
    - Have You Forgotten, Marguerite? composer: C. M. Denison/E. Fred Dusenberrry publisher: Mills (Middletown, NY), 1913 (Box 45, Item 74)
    - I Want You composer: Geo. M. Cohan/Same publisher: F. A. Mills, 1907 (Box 45, Item 75)
    - I'll Wait For You 'Till the Cows Come Home composer: Thos. A. Allen/Same publisher: Daly (Boston), 1911 (Box 45, Item 76)
    - It Makes Me Think of Home Sweet Home composer: Frank D. Bryan/Same publisher: Chas. K. Harris, 1904 (Box 45, Item 77)
    - It Takes a Little Rain With the Sunshine to Make the World Go Round composer: Ballard Macdonald/Harry Carroll publisher: Shapiro, Bernstein, 1913 (Box 45, Item 78)
    - Just A Little Smile composer: Jos. E. Howard/Same publisher: Chas. K. Harris, 1911 (Box 45, Item 79)
    - Just Across the Bridge of Gold composer: Andrew B. Sterling/Harry Von Tilzer publisher: Harry Von Tilzer, 1905 (Box 45, Item 80)
    - Just Across the Bridge of Years composer: C. M. Denison/A. J. Holmes publisher: Holmes (Middletown, NY), 191? (Box 45, Item 81)
    - Just At the Break of Day composer: Harry J. Lincoln/Same publisher: Vandersloot (Williamsport, Pa.), 1905 (Box 45, Item 82)
    - Just You composer: Con Barth/Same publisher: A. J. Stasny, 1917 (Box 45, Item 83)
    - Katie's Eyes Are Irish composer: J. Hayden Clarendon/St. Antony Johnstone publisher: Jos. W. Stern, 1904 (Box 45, Item 84)
    - Keep A Little Cosy Corner in Your Heart For Me composer: Jack Drislane/Theodore Morse publisher: F. B. Haviland, 1905 (Box 45, Item 85)
    - Keep on the Sunny Side composer: Jack Drislane/Theodore Morse publisher: F. B. Haviland, 1906 (Box 45, Item 86)
    - The King of the Deep Am I composer: W. C. Kreusch/Same publisher: Leo Feist, 1901 (Box 45, Item 87)
    - Kiss of Spring composer: Phil Staats/Walter Rolfe publisher: Walter Jacobs (Boston), 1910 (Box 45, Item 88)
    - Lay My Wedding Dress Away composer: Arthur J. Lamb/Albert Von Tilzer publisher: York, 1904 (Box 45, Item 89)
    - Leaf By Leaf the Roses Fall composer: Beth Slater Whitson/W. R. Williams publisher: Will Rossiter (Chicago), 1911 (Box 45, Item 90)
    - Let It Alone composer: Alex Rogers/Bert A. Williams publisher: Gotham-Attucks, 1906 (Box 45, Item 91)
    - Let Me Hear the Songs My Mother Used to Sing composer: Janet Gordon/Edw. Gabriel publisher: Frank K. Root, 1906 (Box 45, Item 92)
    - A Little Bunch of Shamrocks composer: Andrew Sterling & Wm. Jerome/Harry Von Tilzer publisher: Harry von Tilzer, 1913 (Box 45, Item 93)
    - Lord! Have Mercy on a Married Man composer: Edgar Leslie/J. Fred. Helf publisher: J. Fred Helf, 1910 (Box 45, Item 94)
    - Love Me and the World is Mine composer: Dave Reed, Jr./Ernest R. Ball publisher: M. Witmark & Sons, 1906 (Box 45, Item 95)
    - Love Me While the Loving is Good composer: Stanley Murphy/Harry Von Tilzer publisher: Harry Von Tilzer, 1913 (Box 45, Item 96)
    - Love's Old Sweet Song composer: C. Clifton Bingham/J. L. Molloy publisher: Huntington Piano Co. (Shelton, CT), undated (Box 45, Item 97)
    - Love's Old Sweet Song composer: C. Clifton Bingham/J. L. Molloy publisher: Sterling (Piano) Co. (Derby, CT), undated (Box 45, Item 98)
    - Lovie Dear composer: Fred Bonny/Tom Lemonier publisher: Rogers Bros., 1911 (Box 45, Item 99)
    - The Man Behind composer: Vincent Bryan/J. B. Mullen publisher: Shapiro, Remick, 1904 (Box 45, Item 100)
    - Maybe Sometime composer: Jack Drislane/Theodore Morse publisher: F. B. Haviland, 1906 (Box 45, Item 101)
    - Meet Me At Twilight composer: Sydney P. Harris/Same publisher: Sydney P. Harris, 1914 (Box 45, Item 102)
    - Meet Me In St. Louis, Louis composer: Andrew B. Sterling/Kerry Mills publisher: F. A. Mills, 1904 (Box 45, Item 103)
    - Meet Me Tonight In Dreamland composer: Beth Slater Whitson/Leo Friedman publisher: Will Rossiter (Chicago), 1909 (Box 45, Item 104)
    - Meet Me Where the Lantern's Glow composer: Manuel Klein/Same publisher: M. Witmark & Sons, 1909 (Box 45, Item 105)
    - Mickey composer: Harry Williams/Neil Moret publisher: Waterson, Berlin & Snyder, 1919 (Box 45, Item 106)
    - 'Mid the Fields of Snowy Cotton ('Round My Dear Old Southern Home) composer: Otto and John Heinzman publisher: Weser Bros., 1906 (Box 45, Item 107)
    - Mister, You're Smokin' Again composer: Ernest Tenney/Same publisher: Howley, Haviland & Dresser, 1903 (Box 45, Item 108)
    - Moonlight Bay composer: Edward Madden/Percy Wenrich publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1912 (Box 45, Item 109)
    - The Moonlight, The Rose and You composer: Chas.E. Bae/Johann C. Schmid publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1910 (Box 45, Item 110)
    - My Baby Just Cares For Me composer: Gus Kahn/Walter Donaldson publisher: Donaldson, Douglas & Gumble, 1930 (Box 45, Item 111)
    - My Heart Has Learned to Love You, Now Do Not Say 'Goodbye' composer: Dave Reed/Eniest R Ball publisher: M. Witmark & Sons, 1910 (Box 45, Item 112)
    - My Irish Girl composer: Alfred Bryan/H. Blanke- Belcher publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1911 (Box 45, Item 113)
    - My Irish Molly 0 composer: Wm. Jerome/Jean Schwartz publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1905 (Box 45, Item 114)
    - My Old Gal From Alabam' composer: Olive L. Frields/Harry L. Newman publisher: Sunlight (Chicago), 1913 (Box 45, Item 115)
    - My Old Home On the Hill composer: S. J. Williams/Same publisher: Empire (Boston), 1912 (Box 45, Item 116)
    - My Pretty Factory Maid composer: Robert Stagg/Same publisher: Robert Stagg (Danbury), 1905 (Box 45, Item 117)
    - My Rose From the Garden of Girls composer: Beth Slater Whitson/W. R. Williams publisher: Will Rossiter (Chicago), 1911 (Box 45, Item 118)
    - My Rose Marie composer: James A. MacElwee/Same publisher: Church, Paxson & Co., 1908 (Box 45, Item 119)
    - My Wife's Gone to the Country. Hurrah! Hurrah! composer: George Whiting & Irving Berlin/Ted Snyder publisher: Ted Snyder, 1909 (Box 45, Item 120)
    - No Wedding Bells For Me composer: E. P. Moran & Will A. Heelan/Seymour Furth publisher: Shapiro, 1906 (Box 45, Item 121)
    - Not 'Till Then (Will I Cease to Love You) composer: Charles K. Harris/Same publisher: Charles K. Harris, undated (Box 45, Item 122)
    - Nothing New Beneath the Sun composer: Geo. M. Cohan/Same publisher: F. A. Mills, 1906 (Box 45, Item 123)
    - Nothing to Do Until To-Morrow composer: Jack Drislane/Geo.W. Meyer publisher: F. B. Haviland, 1911 (Box 45, Item 124)
    - Oh, Mr. Dream Man (Please Let Me Dream Some More) composer: Jimmie V. Monaco/Same publisher: Harry Von Tilzer, 1911 (Box 45, Item 125)
    - Oh, What a Difference in the Morning composer: Felix McGlennon/Same publisher: Oliver Ditson/1891, 1905 (Box 45, Item 126)
    - Oh, You Beautiful Doll composer: Brown/Nat D. AYemour publisher: Joseph H. Remick, 1911 (Box 45, Item 127)
    - Oh, You Million Dollar Doll composer: Grant Clarke & Edgar Leslie/Maurice Abrahams Jean C. Havez/Geo. publisher: Maurice Abrahams, 1913 (Box 45, Item 128)
    - Oh, You Silv'ry Bells composer: Botsford publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1912 (Box 45, Item 129)
    - The Old Maid's Ball composer: Irving Berlin/Same publisher: Waterson, Berlin & Snyder, 1913 (Box 45, Item 130)
    - The Old New England Homestead in the Dell composer: Henry Balch Ingram/Same publisher: Henry B. Ingram (Kingston, N.Y.), 1904 (Box 45, Item 131)
    - On a Good Old Time Sleigh Ride Andrew K. Allison/Albert tumble composer: publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1913 (Box 45, Item 132)
    - On Mobile Bay composer: Earle C. Jones/Chas. N. Daniels publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1910 (Box 45, Item 133)
    - One Year Ago To-Night composer: Dan J. Sullivan/Same publisher: George M. Krey (Boston), 1906 (Box 45, Item 134)
    - The Only Pal I Ever Had Came From 'Frisco Town composer: Earle C. Jones/Charles N. Daniels publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1911 (Box 45, Item 135)
    - Papa, Please Buy Me an Airship composer: Ren Shields/Kerry Mills publisher: F. A. Mills, 1909 (Box 45, Item 136)
    - Peg 0' My Heart composer: Alfred Bryan/Fred Fisher publisher: Leo. Feist, 1913 (Box 45, Item 137)
    - Play That Barber Shop Chord composer: Wm. Tracey/Lewis F. Muir publisher: J. Fred Helf, 1910 (Box 45, Item 138)
    - Please, Miss Central, Find My Mamma composer: Charles K. Harris publisher: Charles K. Harris, 1913 (Box 45, Item 139)
    - Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm composer: A. Seymour Brown/Albert Gumble publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1914 (Box 45, Item 140)
    - Red Cloud composer: W. A. Lang/A. Fred Phillips publisher: Ernest S. Williams (Boston), 1909 (Box 45, Item 141)
    - Red Wing (An Indian Fable) composer: Thurland Chattaway/Kerry Mills publisher: F. A. Mills, 1907 (Box 45, Item 142)
    - A Ring on the Finger is Worth Two on the Phone composer: Jack Mahoney/Geo.W. Meyer publisher: F. B. Haviland, 1911 (Box 45, Item 143)
    - Rosebud (Call and I'll Come to You) composer: Will D. Cobb/Same publisher: F.A. Mills, 1906 (Box 45, Item 144)
    - Roses Bring Dreams of You composer: Herbert Ingraham/Same publisher: Shapiro, 1908 (Box 45, Item 145)
    - School Days (When We Were a Couple of Kids) composer: Will. D. Cobb/Gus Edwards publisher: Gus Edwards, 1907 (Box 45, Item 146)
    - Silver Bell composer: Edward Madden/Percy Wenrich publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1910 (Box 45, Item 147)
    - Silver Threads Among the Gold composer: Eben E. Rexford/H. P. Danks publisher: Hamilton S. Gordon/(1873), 1901 (Box 45, Item 148)
    - Since We Said Goodbye composer: George Hamilton/Will A. Heelan publisher: T. B. Harms, 1900 (Box 45, Item 149)
    - Sing Me the Rosary composer: Rober Lewis/F. Henri Klickmann publisher: Frnk K. Root, 1913 (Box 45, Item 150)
    - Smiles (That Makes Us Happy) composer: J. Will Callahan/Lee S. Roberts publisher: Jerome H. Remick/(1917), 1918 (Box 45, Item 151)
    - Somebody Else, It's Always Somebody Else composer: Jack Drislane/Geo. W. Meyer publisher: F. B. Haviland, 1910 (Box 45, Item 152)
    - Somebody Else Will If You Don't composer: Alfred Bryan/Albert Gumble publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1912 (Box 45, Item 153)
    - Somebody Loves Somebody composer: Bert Potter/Same publisher: George M. Krey (Boston), 1906 (Box 45, Item 154)
    - Somebody's Coming to My House composer: Irving Berlin/Same publisher: Waterson, Berlin & Snyder, 1913 (Box 45, Item 155)
    - Somebody's Waiting For Me composer: Andrew B. Sterling/Harry Von Tilzer publisher: Leo Feist, 1902 (Box 45, Item 156)
    - Somewhere composer: Charles K. Harris/Same publisher: Charles K. Harris, 1906 (Box 45, Item 157)
    - The Songs of Ages composer: Jerome Heller/Same publisher: Church, Paxson & Co., 1914 (Box 45, Item 158)
    - Sparkling Eyes composer: Will L. Livernash/Same publisher: Daly (Boston), 1911 (Box 45, Item 159)
    - The Star Spangled Banner composer: Francis Scott Key/Samuel Arnold publisher: Alfred Fox Piano Company, undated (Box 45, Item 160)
    - Starlight composer: Edward Madden/Theodore Morse publisher: F. B. Haviland, 1905 (Box 45, Item 161)
    - Strolling Home With Jennie composer: Thos. S. Allen/Same publisher: Walter Jacobs (Boston), 1906 (Box 45, Item 162)
    - Sugar Moon composer: Stanley Murphy/Percy Wenrich publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1910 (Box 45, Item 163)
    - Suppose I Met You Face to Face composer: Charles K. Harris/Same publisher: Charles K. Harris, 1913 (Box 45, Item 164)
    - Sweet Angel, Whisper Low composer: Unknown/Blanche Gould Ebbert publisher: Sterling Piano Co. (Brooklyn), 1900 (Box 45, Item 165)
    - Sweet Eileen Asthore composer: James I. Russell publisher: M. Witmark & Sons, 1912 (Box 45, Item 166)
    - The Sweetest Girl in Dixie composer: James O'Dea/R. J. Adams publisher: Shapiro, Remick & Co., 1903 (Box 45, Item 167)
    - Sweetest Mem'ries of Courting Days composer: Harry D. Kerr/Same publisher: Vinton (Boston), 1911 (Box 45, Item 168)
    - Take a Little Ride With Me (A Conversation With Music, Between an Automobilist and a Dairy Maid) composer: Jack Drislane/Theodore Morse publisher: F. B. Haviland, 1906 (Box 45, Item 169)
    - Take a Little Tip From Father composer: Irving Berlin and Ted Snyder publisher: Ted Snyder (Waterson, Berlin & Snyder), 1912 (Box 45, Item 170)
    - Take a Vacation Mr. Moon composer: Bert Kalmar/Ted Snyder publisher: Ted Snyder, 1911 (Box 45, Item 171)
    - Take Me Back to the Garden of Love composer: E. Ray Goetz/Nat. Osborne publisher: Ted Snyder, 1911 (Box 45, Item 172)
    - Take Me In Your Arms Again Charles K. Harris/Same composer: publisher: Charles K. Harris, 1912 (Box 45, Item 173)
    - The Tale the Church Bells Tolled Harry Williams/Egbert Van composer: Alstyne publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1907 (Box 45, Item 174)
    - Tell Me With Your Eyes composer: Arthur J. Lamb/Albert Von Tilzer publisher: York Music, 1904 (Box 45, Item 175)
    - Temple Bells (In the Soft Moonlight) composer: Manuel Klein/Same publisher: M. Witmark & Sons, 1912 (Box 45, Item 176)
    - Tennessee Moon composer: Jack Mahoney/Percy Wenrich publisher: Wenrich-Howard, 1912 (Box 45, Item 177)
    - That Dixie Rag composer: Chas.L Melcher/Edw. M O Keefe publisher: Fred G. Heberlein, 1911 (Box 45, Item 178)
    - That Dreamy Italian Waltz composer: Jos. McCarthy/Al. Piantadosi publisher: Leo Feist, 1910 (Box 45, Item 179)
    - That Mesmerizing Mendelssohn Tune composer: Irving Berlin/Same publisher: Ted Snyder, 1909 (Box 45, Item 180)
    - That Mysterious Rag composer: Irving Berlin and Ted Snyder publisher: Ted Snyder, 1911 (Box 45, Item 181)
    - That Old Girl of Mine composer: Earle C. Jones/Egbert Van Alstyne publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1912 (Box 45, Item 182)
    - That's a Funny Place to Kiss a Girl composer: Dick Richards/Leon. Kimberly publisher: F. B. Haviland, 1912 (Box 45, Item 183)
    - That's How I Need You composer: Joe McCarthy & Joe Goodwin/Al Piantadosi publisher: Leo Feist, 1912 (Box 45, Item 184)
    - That's Why the Violets Live composer: Jack Mahoney/Theodore Morse publisher: Theodore Morse, 1913 (Box 45, Item 185)
    - There's a Girl in the Heart of Maryland (With a Heart That Belongs to Me) composer: Ballard Macdonald/Harry Carroll publisher: Shapiro, Bernstein, 1913 (Box 45, Item 186)
    - There's a Mother Old and Gray who needs Me Now composer: Geo. H. Diamond/Same publisher: Harold Rossiter (Chicago), undated (Box 45, Item 187)
    - There's Nothing Like a Mother's Love composer: W.A.Lang/May Greene. publisher: Daly (Boston), 1911 (Box 45, Item 188)
    - Those Songs My Mother Used to Sing composer: H. Wakefield Smith/Same publisher: M. Witmark & Sons, 1904 (Box 45, Item 189)
    - Till the Sands of the Desert Grow Cold composer: Geo.Graff, Jr./Ernest R. Ball publisher: M. Witmark & Sons, undated (Box 45, Item 190)
    - Tipperary composer: Leo Curley/Jas. M. Fulton & J. Fred. Helf publisher: Helf & Hager, 1907 (Box 45, Item 191)
    - The Trail of the Lonesome Pine composer: Ballard Macdonald/Harry Carroll publisher: Shapiro, Bernstein, 1913 (Box 45, Item 192)
    - Two Little Baby Shoes composer: Edward Madden/Theodore Morse publisher: E. G. Haviland, 1907 (Box 45, Item 193)
    - Under the Yum Yum Tree composer: Andrew B. Sterling/Harry Von Tilzer publisher: Harry Von Tilzer, 1910 (Box 45, Item 194)
    - Violette composer: Dolly Jardon/James B. Mullen publisher: P. J. Howley, 1905 (Box 45, Item 195)
    - Wait 'Till the Sun Shines, Nellie composer: Andrew B. Sterling/Harry Von Tilzer publisher: Harry Von Tilzer, 1905 (Box 45, Item 196)
    - Waiting for the Robert E. Lee composer: L.Wolfe Gilbert/Lewis F. Muir publisher: F.A. Mills, 1912 (Box 45, Item 197)
    - Way Down South composer: George Fairman/Same publisher: Tell Taylor, 1912 (Box 45, Item 198)
    - We'll Never Let Our Old Flag Fall composer: Albert E. MacNutt/M.F. Kelly publisher: John Hanna (Chappell & Co.), 1915 (Box 45, Item 199)
    - What D'ye Mean You Lost Yer Dog? (Where's That Dog-gone Dog-gone Dog of Mine) composer: Thos. S. Allen/Joseph M. Daly publisher: Jerome Remick, 1913 (Box 45, Item 200)
    - What You goin' to Do When the Rent Comes 'Round? (Rufus Rastus Johnson Brown) composer: Andrew B. Sterling/Harry Von Tilzer publisher: Harry Von Tilzer, 1905 (Box 45, Item 201)
    - When I First Met You composer: Sam M. Lewis/Geo.W. Meyer publisher: Geo. M Meyer, 1913 (Box 45, Item 202)
    - When It's Apple Blossom Time in Normandie composer: Mellor Gifford and Trevor publisher: Jerome Remick, 1912 (Box 45, Item 203)
    - When It's Moonlight Mary Darling `Heath the Old Grape Arbor Shade composer: Bartley Costello/J. Fred Helf publisher: Helf & Hager, 1907 (Box 45, Item 204)
    - When Mr. Cupid Comes To Town composer: Bobby Heath/Chas. Odonnell publisher: Newton B. Heims, 1911 (Box 45, Item 205)
    - When Summer Tells Autumn Good-bye composer: Arthur J. Lamb/J. Fred Helf publisher: Helf & Hager, 1906 (Box 45, Item 206)
    - When the Band Played "My country 'Tis of Thee" composer: Matt. Silvey/Harry L. Newman publisher: Jos. J. Kaiser, 1905 (Box 45, Item 207)
    - When the Bees Are in the Hive composer: Alfred Bryan/Kerry Mills publisher: F. A. Mills, 1904 (Box 45, Item 208)
    - When the Dew is On the Rose composer: Anita Owen/Same publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1911 (Box 45, Item 209)
    - When the Evening Breeze is Sighing "Home Sweet Home" composer: J. Hayden-Clarendon/Alfred Solman publisher: Jos. W. Stern, 1905 (Box 45, Item 210)
    - When the Flowers Bloom in Springtime (Molly Dear) composer: Andrew B. Sterling/Harry Von Tilzer publisher: Harry Von Tilzer, 1906 (Box 45, Item 211)
    - When the Golden Leaves Are Falling composer: Charles K. Harris publisher: Charles K. Harris, 1911 (Box 45, Item 212)
    - When the Harbor Lights are Burning composer: Alfred Bryan/Alfred Solman publisher: Jos. W. Stern, 1907 (Box 45, Item 213)
    - When the Old Mill Stream is Sleeping composer: Sam M. Lewis/Dave Rose publisher: Willis Woodward, 1907 (Box 45, Item 214)
    - When the Roses Bloom in Dixie Land composer: George Evans/Same publisher: Chas. K. Harris, 1913 (Box 45, Item 215)
    - When the Song Birds Sing Their Home Sweet Home Again composer: Art. Bucknam/Same publisher: Empire (Boston), 1907 (Box 45, Item 216)
    - When the Snowbirds Cross the Valley composer: Monroe H. Rosenfeld/Alfred Solman publisher: Jos. W. Stern, 1906 (Box 45, Item 217)
    - When the Sun Shines on the Rive in September composer: Theodore R. Lyons/Charles G. Love publisher: Globe, 1913 (Box 45, Item 218)
    - When They Gather in the Sheaves composer: Chas. E. Baer/Johann C. Schmid publisher: Vandersloot (Williamsport, Pa. ), 1911 (Box 45, Item 219)
    - When We Were Sweethearts Coming Thro' the Rye composer: Thos. S. Allen/Same publisher: O'Neil & Story (Boston), 1911 (Box 45, Item 220)
    - When You're Away composer: Seymour Brown & Joe Young/Bert Grant publisher: Jerome Remick, 1911 (Box 45, Item 221)
    - Where the Morning Glories Twine Around the Door composer: Andrew B. Sterling/Harry Von Tilzer publisher: Harry Von Tilzer, 1905 (Box 45, Item 222)
    - Where the Red, Red, Roses Grow composer: Wm. Jerome/Jean Schwartz publisher: Jerome & Schwartz, 1913 (Box 45, Item 223)
    - Where the River Shannon Flows composer: James I. Russell/Same publisher: M. Witmark & Sons, 1906 (Box 45, Item 224)
    - Where the Silv'ry Colorado Wends Its Way composer: C. H. Scoggins/Chas. Avril publisher: Will Rossiter (Chicago), 1903 (Box 45, Item 225)
    - While the Old Mill Wheel is Turning composer: Will D. Cobb/Kerry Mills publisher: F. A. Mills, 1906 (Box 45, Item 226)
    - Whistling Jim (That's Him) composer: D. A. Esrom/Theodore Morse publisher: Theodore Morse, 1912 (Box 45, Item 227)
    - Why don't They Play With Me? composer: Charles K. Harris/Same publisher: Charles K. Harris, 1904 (Box 45, Item 228)
    - Wild Cherries (That Cooney Spooney Rag) composer: Irving Berlin/Ted Snyder publisher: Ted Snyder, 1909 (Box 45, Item 229)
    - Will the Roses Bloom in Heaven? composer: Charles K. Harris publisher: Charles K. Harris, 1911 (Box 45, Item 230)
    - Will You Love Me in December As You Do in May? composer: J.J Walker/Ernest R. Ball publisher: M. Witmark & Sons, 1905 (Box 45, Item 231)
    - Won't You Come Over to My House composer: Harry Williams/Egbert Van Alstyne publisher: Jerome H. Remick, 1906 (Box 45, Item 232)
    - Won't You Let Me Take You Home? composer: Eddie Doerr/Lou Lashley publisher: Royal, 1912 (Box 45, Item 233)
    - Won't You Waltz "Home Sweet Home" With Me For Old Times Sake composer: Herbert Ingraham/Same publisher: Shapiro, 1907 (Box 45, Item 234)
    - Would You Care? composer: Charles K. Harris/Same publisher: Charles K. Harris, 1905 (Box 45, Item 235)
    - The Yankee Doodle Boy composer: George M. Cohan/Same publisher: F.A. Mills, 1904 (Box 45, Item 236)
    - Yesterday composer: Charles K. Harris/Same publisher: Charles K. Harris, 1907 (Box 45, Item 237)
    - You Broke My Heart to Pass the Time Away composer: Joe Goodwin/LeoWood publisher: Leo Feist, 1913 (Box 45, Item 238)
    - You're My Baby composer: Seymour Brown/Nat D. Ayer publisher: Jerome Remick, 1912 (Box 45, Item 239)
    - You're the Sweetest Girl in Ireland composer: Bobby Heath/Frank Black publisher: Joe Morris, 1913 (Box 45, Item 240)